taslyus.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy taslyus

The privacy of your personal information is important to Tasly. This Privacy Policy describes what information may collect about you, how we may use your information, how we protect it, and the choices you have on how that information is used. We want you to feel as comfortable as possible visiting our Web sites – we understand that health is a very personal, private subject. 

As our privacy policy changes in significant ways, we will post privacy policy changes on our Web sites in a timely manner. 

When we refer to ourselves as "we" or "Tasly” we mean our entire company, including any company that we control (for example, a subsidiary that we own). We may share information among companies that we own or control, and we may share information with our co-promotion partners, and companies working with but all information we share will be protected under the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**Collection of Personal Information**

Visitors to each of our Web sites can access the Web site's home page, and browse some areas of the site, without disclosing any personally identifiable information. We do not collect personally identifiable information through the Web site unless you intentionally provide it to us. Visitors registering on our Web sites are asked to provide identifying information, such as name and contact information. On the registration screen, we label which information is required for registration. 

Through the use of “cookies” and other technologies, we do track information provided to us by your browser, including the Web site you came from (known as the referring URL), your IP address, the type of browser you use, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser. Cookies are used to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. This information is used to evaluate visitors' use of the Website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for us. You may reject cookies by accessing the “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers, which will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive cookies, and how to disable cookies altogether. Note that if you reject or block cookies, it may affect your ability to enjoy the full functionality and experience of our Website. 

We may collect information about health care professionals from other sources to verify licensure status and identity. In some cases, we ask customers for information after they register, such as credit card information. Where necessary (for example, to process an order for a purchase), our Web sites may contact financial or credit organizations to confirm customer credit card information. 

We may augment our existing user databases with legally obtained information from third parties. Some of this information may be personally identifiable, such as national change of address information. We also collect information that you voluntarily provide to us through responses to surveys, search functions, questionnaires, and feedback. We may ask you to provide additional information such as your e-mail address if you want to obtain additional services or information or to resolve complaints or concerns. 

Cookies, log files, and pixel-tags may be used by the Tasly Web sites to identify a user as the user moves through our Web sites. Your browser allows us to place some information on your computer's hard drive that identifies the computer you are using. 

**Use of Your Information**

We gather data about visitors to our Web sites for product and service development and improvement of our offerings. We may also use it for market analysis. We may provide information from our Web sites in aggregate form, with identifying information removed, to third parties. 

We may target our marketing and health care messaging depending on information we have about you. For example, a user we know is a woman undergoing menopause may receive information on products targeted at women undergoing menopause. We may send information to you that we may believe will benefit you, including information about any Tasly products. 

**How Tasly Handles Information**

We have put in place commercially reasonably procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. We have technology and security policies and other measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, and accidental loss. We also protect your information by requiring that all our employees and others who have access to or are associated with the processing of your data respect your confidentiality. 

Personally identifiable health information you share with us is stored on our servers or hosted by third parties who have entered into agreements with us that require them to observe our Privacy Policy. Our servers are designed to be physically secure and protected from unauthorized access by unauthorized persons. 

Information in our servers is backed up routinely, in order to aid in the recovery of information in the event of accidental damage of information or due to a natural disaster. The backup is protected and secured. 

We may release account and other personal information when we believe release is in our judgment necessary to comply with law or legal process, to protect or defend our rights or property or those of our users, to protect the personal safety of our users or the public, or to provide to our attorneys, accountants, regulators, auditors or other advisors. We may release personal health information if, in our judgment the release is compelled by law or regulation, or if the release may be necessary to prevent the death or serious injury of an individual. 

**Your Privacy Choices**

When you complete registration of an offer from us, you may be given the option of receiving recurring informational/promotional e-mail from. You may opt-out from receiving this e-mail when you provide the information or follow the instructions as mentioned in the e-mail or included in each message we send to you. 

**Email**

We appreciate your questions and comments about our [Rolex Submariner Replica Watches](http://www.watchnreplica.com/category/fake-rolex-submariner/) and services and welcome your e-mails and questions. We will share your messages with those within our organization that are most capable of addressing the issues contained in your message. We may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it, but your e-mail address and message will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Submitting your address anywhere on the Website may result in your e-mail address being added to our e-mail list. You may unsubscribe at any time by opting out of e-mail subscriptions with the “unsubscribe” link included in each e-mail. 

**Updating Your Personal Information**

You can always contact us in order to remove the personal information that you have provided to us from our systems, update the personal information that you have provided to us, and change your preferences with respect to marketing contacts by e-mailing us at hrus@tasly.com.
